pokersavvy.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy Statement | PokerSavvy

**Overall privacy statement**

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certaintypes of information about our users, we want to help you understand the termsand conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. Thisprivacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it,and how to correct or change it.

 **1\. What information does** **Poker** **Savvycollect?**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is toprovide you with the best and most useful content and services. Several of theservices and features that we offer on our site requiresyou to provide us with information as a condition of usage. These includeearning SavvyPoints and participating in certain tournaments.

We collect personally identifiable information, such as yourname, email address, postal address and phone number when you provide it to us.From time to time, we may also collect other sensitive information such as yourjob title, gender, username and password. We may also receive information aboutyou from other sources and add it to the information you provided to us.

Once you register with PokerSavvyyou are no longer anonymous to us.

 **2\. What is PokerSavvy's practice regarding cookies?**

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, whichstores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Youdo not need to have cookies turned on to visit our site, although activeparticipation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alonetell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personallyidentifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance yourservices in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on yourbrowser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.

We also use technologies, including electronic images knownas Web bugs-sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, orbeacons-that allow us to track general user-traffic patterns. We alsoautomatically receive and record information from our servers and from yourbrowser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on oursite, and information about pages you visited. Unless you have registered forone of our products or services, the information we gather through the use oftracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiableinformation about you.

We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety ofways, including: 

  * Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites; 
  * Tracking friend referrals;
  * Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage; 
  * Determining which features our overall user population likes best; 
  * Saving your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites; 
  * Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content based on your interests.

 **3\. How does PokerSavvy usethe information?**

We use the information we gather for four general purposes: 

  * To customize the advertising and the content you see; 
  * To enhance the user experience in our site. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you; 
  * To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling you to participate in paid services, polls, contests, and message boards; 
  * To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.

 **4\. How does PokerSavvyshare the information?**

We will make your personally identifiable informationavailable to other companies or people when: 

  * You have elected to allow us to share that information at the time that you registered with us or provided us the information, or through a subsequent affirmative election through our website. 
  * You volunteer information or create a public profile in the course of your participation in our community features such as forums and user opinions and reviews
  * You use cobranded services (i.e., sites or services that we offer to you in connection with a partner, who is identified on the site). When you use a cobranded service within our site, you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. 
  * We hire third-party vendors to provide specialized services such as customer support; email message deployment; suppression, merge and de-duplication services; data processing; and special products or services that you have requested. These companies are only allowed to use the information in order to help us fulfill our services to you. We do not provide your information to these companies for their own, permanent use. 
  * You unsubscribe for a mailing that we send to you on behalf of a third party. We may share your removal instruction with the third party so that it may be added to that person's list of people to whom they may not send emails. 
  * You are the winner of a contest or a sweepstakes that is co-sponsored with a third party and that third party needs your information in order to manage the prize fulfillment process. 
  * When required by law, such as when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 
  * We believe that your actions violate applicable laws, PokerSavvy's Terms of Use, or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others.

 **Aggregate information**

We aggregate personally identifiable information anddisclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner toadvertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and otherpurposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could beused to identify you personally.

 **Business transfers**

We are always seeking to improve our web sites and ourbusiness. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, orone or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or beacquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or allof your information as a part of the sale in order that the service beingprovided to you may continue or for other business purposes.

 **5\. What are my options?**

Users who would rather not provide any of the user datarequested by our registration process do not need to register with us. You canstill view much of the content and use many of the services offered by oursites without registering.

We also give users the following options: 

**Opting not to receive our electronicnewsletters or those of third parties when registering.**

  * Users who opt in may remove themselves from mailing lists at any time through the subscription-management pages or by following the instructions at the end of the e-mail they received from us; 
  * Opting not to provide certain personal information when registering for a site, provided, however, that you may not be able to use some of our products or services without providing us with certain information.

 **6\. How can I review and update my personally identifiableinformation?**

You can review, correct, or change the information collectedduring registration in the manage account section of My PokerSavvy.Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. Users whoare experiencing problems with our services or who have questions about how ourservices work can contact us using e-mail addresses at the bottom of this page.

 **7\. How will I know if the privacy policy is changed?**

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflectedfirst within this area of our site.
